Department of Physical Education and Athletics Records UA046
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, negatives, and Scientific Baseball (manual), 1870 -- 2013; 1950 -- 1990; UA046.003; 29.8 Linear Feet; 490 Digital Object(s)
  - Men's basketball, 1970 -- 1972; UA046.003.036.00086 (Box 36)
  - Men's basketball, 1972 -- 1973; UA046.003.036.00087 (Box 36)
    - Men's basketball team, 1973; UA046.003.036.00087.00001; Unknown (Box 36)
      Back row: (left to right) Assistant Coach Sam Bryant; Nick de Kanter, manager; Leroy Charles; Bruce Bernstein; Dennis Mink; Willie ratchford; Eddie Tapscott; Coach Tim Penders. Seated: David Robbins; George Powell; Reggie Graham; Artie Ryce. Front Row: Tri-Captains John White; Willie Young; and Paul Daniels
      Basketball (Men's); Athletics; People; Portraits, Group; photographic print; Bryant, Sam
  - Men's basketball, 1973; UA046.003.036.00088 (Box 36)
  - Men's basketball, 1973 -- 1974; UA046.003.036.00089 (Box 36)
    - Tufts basketball co-captain Ed Tapscott, 1973 -- 1974; UA046.003.036.00089.00001; Unknown (Box 36)
      Athletics; Basketball (Men's); photographic print; Black students; Tapscott, Ed
    - Ed Tapscott with coach Tom Penders and assistant coach Sam Bryant, 1973 -- 1974; UA046.003.036.00089.00002; Unknown (Box 36)
      People; Athletics; Basketball (Men's); photographic print; Tapscott, Ed
  - Men's basketball, 1974; UA046.003.036.00090 (Box 36)
  - Women's basketball, 1974; UA046.003.036.00091 (Box 36)
  - Men's basketball, 1974 -- 1975; UA046.003.036.00092 (Box 36)
  - Men's basketball, 1974 -- 1976; UA046.003.036.00093 (Box 36)
  - Women's basketball, 1975; UA046.003.036.00094 (Box 36)
  - Men's basketball, 1975 -- 1976; UA046.003.036.00095 (Box 36)
  - Women's basketball, 1975 -- 1976; UA046.003.036.00096 (Box 36)
  - Men's basketball, 1976 -- 1977; UA046.003.036.00097 (Box 36)
  - Women's basketball, 1976 -- 1977; UA046.003.036.00098 (Box 36)
  - Men's basketball, 1977 -- 1978; UA046.003.036.00099 (Box 36)
  - Men's basketball, 1978 -- 1979; UA046.003.036.00100 (Box 36)
    - Tufts men's basketball team, 1978 -- 1979; UA046.003.036.00100.00001; Unknown (Box 36)
      Front row, from left to right: Bob Hendrick (manager), Rafael Toro, Steve Shenfeld, Doug Harris, Jim Campbell, Kevin O'Brien, Scott Brown, Mike Rosen (manager). Second row, from left to right: Matt Kauffman (manager), R.C. Pruitt (assistant coach), Bryan Sindorf, Jon Shevell, George Mazareas, Benji Williams, Mark Craigwell, Ron Woods, John Caragiorgis, Mark Doughtie (trainer), John White (head coach).
      Athletics; Basketball (Men's); photographic print; Woods, Ronnie; Tufts University
  - Men's basketball, 1971 -- 1972; UA046.003.036.00101 (Box 36)
  - Women's basketball, 1978 -- 1979; UA046.003.036.00102 (Box 36)
  - Men's basketball, 1979 -- 1980; UA046.003.036.00103 (Box 36)
    - Tufts men's basketball team, 1979 -- 1980; UA046.003.036.00103.00001 (Box 36)
      Front: Matt Doughtie. Front row, left to right: Rafael Toro, Charlie Neal, Scott Brown, Bob Bigelow (assistant coach), Jim Campbell (captain), John White (coach), Phil Moran, Doug Harris, Steve Shenfeld. Second row, from left to right: Mike Rosen (manager), Benji Williams, George Mazareas, Troy Cooper, John Caragiorgis, Bill Ewing, Charlie Schwartz, John Shevell (manager).
      Athletics; Basketball (Men's); photographic print; Tufts University
  - Women's basketball, 1979 -- 1980; UA046.003.036.00104 (Box 36)
  - Women's basketball, 1980 -- 1989; UA046.003.036.00105 (Box 36)
  - Women's basketball, 1980 -- 1983; UA046.003.036.00106 (Box 36)
  - Men's basketball, 1980 -- 1981; UA046.003.036.00107 (Box 36)
  - Men's basketball, 1981 -- 1983; UA046.003.036.00108 (Box 36)
  - Women's basketball, 1982 -- 1983; UA046.003.036.00109 (Box 36)
  - Women's basketball, 1984 -- 1985; UA046.003.036.00110 (Box 36)
  - Women's basketball, 1985 -- 1986; UA046.003.036.00111 (Box 36)
  - Women's basketball, 1986 -- 1987; UA046.003.036.00112 (Box 36)
  - Men's basketball, 1987 -- 1989; UA046.003.036.00113 (Box 36)
  - Women's basketball, 1988 -- 1989; UA046.003.036.00114 (Box 36)
  - Men's alumni basketball game, 1989 -- 1990; UA046.003.036.00115 (Box 36)
  - Women's basketball, 1989 -- 1990; UA046.003.036.00116 (Box 36)
  - Golf, UA046.003.036.00117 (Box 36)
  - Golf, 1945; UA046.003.036.00118 (Box 36)
    Date is approximate
  - Golf, 1954; UA046.003.036.00119 (Box 36)
  - Golf, 1958; UA046.003.036.00120 (Box 36)
  - Golf, 1959; UA046.003.036.00121 (Box 36)
  - Golf, 1960; UA046.003.036.00122 (Box 36)
  - Golf identified copies, 1961; UA046.003.036.00123 (Box 36)
  - Golf, 1961; UA046.003.036.00124 (Box 36)
  - Golf, 1963; UA046.003.036.00125 (Box 36)
  - Golf, 1964; UA046.003.036.00126 (Box 36)
  - Golf, 1965; UA046.003.036.00127 (Box 36)
  - Golf, 1967; UA046.003.036.00128 (Box 36)
  - Golf, 1968; UA046.003.036.00129 (Box 36)
  - Golf, 1970; UA046.003.036.00130 (Box 36)
  - Golf, 1971; UA046.003.036.00131 (Box 36)
  - Golf, 1972; UA046.003.036.00132 (Box 36)
  - Golf, 1972 -- 1973; UA046.003.036.00133 (Box 36)
  - Golf, 1974; UA046.003.036.00134 (Box 36)
  - Golf, 1976; UA046.003.036.00135 (Box 36)
  - Golf, 1977; UA046.003.036.00136 (Box 36)
  - Golf, 1979; UA046.003.036.00137 (Box 36)
  - Golf, 1995; UA046.003.036.00138 (Box 36)
  - Hockey, UA046.003.036.00139 (Box 36)
  - Hockey, 1946 -- 1947; UA046.003.036.00140 (Box 36)
  - Hockey, 1947 -- 1948; UA046.003.036.00141 (Box 36)
  - Hockey, 1950 -- 1951; UA046.003.036.00142 (Box 36)
  - Hockey, 1951 -- 1952; UA046.003.036.00143 (Box 36)
  - Hockey, 1953 -- 1954; UA046.003.036.00144 (Box 36)
  - Hockey, 1955; UA046.003.036.00145 (Box 36)
  - Hockey, 1955 -- 1956; UA046.003.036.00146 (Box 36)
  - Hockey, 1956 -- 1957; UA046.003.036.00147 (Box 36)
  - Hockey, 1986 -- 1987; UA046.003.037.00001 (Box 37)
  - Hockey, 1987 -- 1989; UA046.003.037.00002 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, UA046.003.037.00003 (Box 37)
  - Women's lacrosse, UA046.003.037.00004 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1939 -- 1940; UA046.003.037.00005 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse identified copies, 1940 -- 1959; UA046.003.037.00006 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1940 -- 1959; UA046.003.037.00007 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1943; UA046.003.037.00008 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1946; UA046.003.037.00009 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1947; UA046.003.037.00010 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1950 -- 1959; UA046.003.037.00011 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1953; UA046.003.037.00012 (Box 37)
    - Men's lacrosse team coaching staff, 1953; UA046.003.037.00012.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 37)
      People; Athletics; Lacrosse (Men's); Coaches (Athletics); photographic print
  - Men's lacrosse, 1954; UA046.003.037.00013 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1957; UA046.003.037.00014 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse identified copies, 1960 -- 1969; UA046.003.037.00015 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1960 -- 1961; UA046.003.037.00016 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1964; UA046.003.037.00017 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1965; UA046.003.037.00018 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1966; UA046.003.037.00019 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1967; UA046.003.037.00020 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1968; UA046.003.037.00021 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1969; UA046.003.037.00022 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1970; UA046.003.037.00023 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1971; UA046.003.037.00024 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1972; UA046.003.037.00025 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1972 -- 1973; UA046.003.037.00026 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1974; UA046.003.037.00027 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1975; UA046.003.037.00028 (Box 37)
  - Women's lacrosse, 1975; UA046.003.037.00029 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1976; UA046.003.037.00030 (Box 37)
  - Women's lacrosse, 1976; UA046.003.037.00031 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1977; UA046.003.037.00032 (Box 37)
  - Women's lacrosse, 1977; UA046.003.037.00033 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1978; UA046.003.037.00034 (Box 37)
  - Women's lacrosse, 1978; UA046.003.037.00035 (Box 37)
  - Women's lacrosse, 1979; UA046.003.037.00036 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1980; UA046.003.037.00037 (Box 37)
  - Women's lacrosse, 1980; UA046.003.037.00038 (Box 37)
  - Women's lacrosse, 1983; UA046.003.037.00039 (Box 37)
  - Men's lacrosse, 1984 -- 1991; UA046.003.037.00040 (Box 37)
  - Women's lacrosse, 1985; UA046.003.037.00041 (Box 37)
  - Women's lacrosse, 1989; UA046.003.037.00042 (Box 37)
    - Tufts University 1989 undefeated women's lacrosse team (13-0), UA046.003.037.00042.00001; Unknown (Box 37)
      Front row: Stephanie Bower, Becca Knapp, Capt. Jen Lee, Capt. Karin Schott, Capt. Sheryl Bergstein, Laura Manning. Second row: Aryn Landau, Melissa Lowe, Catherine Beldotti, Tove Torgerson, Kim Zinman, Annalisa Gee, Cathy Healy, Trainer Janet Silva. Back row: Asst. Coach Sharon Dawley, Head Coach Carol Rappoli, Moira Connor, Marjorie Kozart, Kris Soucy, Sarah Knowles, Asst. Coach Charlotte Pendergast, Asst. Coach Martha Doherty.
      Lacrosse; Athletics; Students; People; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Women's lacrosses, 1990; UA046.003.037.00043 (Box 37)
    Dates span the decade
  - Sailing, 1955 -- 1981; UA046.003.037.00044 (Box 37)
    - Sailboat on water, 1955; UA046.003.037.00044.00001; Unknown (Box 37)
      Sailing; Sailboats; photographic print
    - Judy Webb leaning on sailboat, 1955; UA046.003.037.00044.00002; Unknown (Box 37)
      People; Sailing; photographic print; Webb, Judy; Dept. of Athletics
    - Judy Webb receiving trophy, 1955; UA046.003.037.00044.00003; Dwight Davis Photo (Box 37)
      Judy Webb receiving a trophy from an unidentified male.
      People; Athletics; photographic print; Webb, Judy; Tufts University; Dept. of Athletics
    - Students sailing, 1981; UA046.003.037.00044.00004; Unknown (Box 37)
      From left to right: Sue Cripe (senior from Jamesville Wisconsin), P. D. Dickey ("Sailor of Year").
      People; Sailing; Sailboats; photographic print; Dept. of Athletics
    - Unidentified men on dock, 1955; UA046.003.037.00044.00005; Unknown (Box 37)
  - Men's and women's sailing, 1939 -- 1959; UA046.003.037.00045 (Box 37)
    - Tufts yacht club (Tufts College sailing team), 1939 -- 1940; UA046.003.037.00045.00001; Unknown (Box 37)
      Photograph of the 1939-1940 Tufts Yacht club (Tufts College sailing team). Left to right: John Bielecki, Charles Cosser, Richard kirkpatrick, Phil Varney.
      Student activities; Athletics; Sailing; photographic print; Bielecki, John; Cosser, Charles; Kirkpatrick, Captain Richard D.; Varney, Phil; Tufts College; Yacht Club
    - Summer school session (Shore school), 1949; UA046.003.037.00045.00002; Unknown (Box 37)
      Student activities; Athletics; Sailing; photographic print; Dept. of Athletics
    - Shore school (Summer school session), 1949; UA046.003.037.00045.00003; Unknown (Box 37)
      Left to right: Dean Nils Wessell, Instructor Theodore Wood, and Wilbert Stevenson, A1950.
      Student activities; Athletics; Sailing; photographic print; Wessell, Nils Yngve; Wood, Theodore; Stevenson, Wilbert E.; Dept. of Athletics
    - Dedication of the yachting clubhouse, 1910 -- 1948; UA046.003.037.00045.00004; Unknown (Box 37)
      Group of men at the dedication of the Tufts yachting clubhouse. Included in the image are Tufts Yacht Club Commodore James B. Lane (A1949) (fourth from left) and Tufts President Leonard Carmichael (fifth from left).
      Student activities; Athletics; Sailing; photographic print; Carmichael, Leonard; Lane, James B.; Dept. of Athletics; Yacht Club
  - Men's sailing, 1910 -- 1966; UA046.003.037.00046 (Box 37)
    - Tufts' sailing team, 1966; UA046.003.037.00046.00001; Unknown (Box 37)
      Front row, from left to right: Ted Schmuhl, Dave Curtis, Charlie Loutrel (captain, holding Coast Guard Academy Alumni Bowl, emblematic of new England championship), Joe Sontz, Stan Chervin, Chuck Whittle. Back row, from left to right: Norman Tubman, Jeff Drazen, Steve Scully, Dave Higginbotham, Kenny Bassett, Craig Black, Jon Winslow, Spud Saunders.
      Athletics; Sailing; photographic print; Tufts University; Dept. of Athletics
    - Dave Curtis receives McMillam Cup, 1910 -- 1966; UA046.003.037.00046.00002; Unknown (Box 37)
      Dave Curtis receiving the McMillam Cup in Annapolis, Maryland.
      People; Athletics; Sailing; photographic print; Tufts University; Dept. of Athletics
    - Tufts summer school, sailing, 1949; UA046.003.037.00046.00003; Unknown (Box 37)
      Professor A. W. Mills. Faculty Advisor to the Yacht Club. Tufts Summer School.
      People; Athletics; Sailing; photographic print; Yacht Club
  - Men's sailing, 1967; UA046.003.037.00047 (Box 37)
    - Tufts sailing team, 1967; UA046.003.037.00047.00001 (Box 37)
      Back row, from left to right: Joseph Duplin (coach), Wayne Prescott, Bob Carruthers, Bill Brown, Kenny Bassett, Dave Curtis (captain), Jon Winslow, Steve Scully, Jon Curtis, Bob Sturges, Dave Higginbotham (assistant coach). Front row, from left to right: Jeff Drazen, Steve Marder, Doug Pote, Tommy Nichols, Charlie Loutrel, Ted Schmuhl, Chuck Whittle, Bruce Kessler.
  - Men's sailing identified copies, 1968; UA046.003.037.00048 (Box 37)
  - Men's sailing, spring, 1968; UA046.003.037.00049 (Box 37)
  - Men's sailing, fall, 1968; UA046.003.037.00050 (Box 37)
    - Tufts varsity sailing team, fall, 1968; UA046.003.037.00050.00001; Unknown (Box 37)
      Front row, from left to right: Dave Arch, Robert Deutsh, Jon Mead, Bill Murphy (co-captain), Dave Curtis (co-captain), George Holley, Dan Phalan. Second Row, from left to right: Joe Duplin (sailing master), Bill Brown, Bill Manning, Richard Dow, Frank Campbell, Brooke Merritt, Bob Carruthers, Bill Garfield, Brad Silsby, Jon Curtis.
  - Men's sailing, spring, 1969; UA046.003.037.00051 (Box 37)
  - Men's sailing, fall, 1969; UA046.003.037.00052 (Box 37)
    - Tufts sailing team, fall, 1969; UA046.003.037.00052.00001; Unknown (Box 37)
      Front row, from left to right: Chris Pollak, Sandy Vietor, Bill Garfield (captain), Chris Andon. Second row, from left to right: Joe Duplin (sailing master), Jim Bunce, Doug Blanding, Andy Edelstein, John Serafini, Lou Libby.
  - Men's sailing, 1970 -- 1979; UA046.003.037.00053 (Box 37)
    - Tufts McMillan Cup Crew and Tufts Kennedy Cup Crew, 1971 -- 1972; UA046.003.037.00053.00001; Unknown (Box 37)
      First row, left to right: Charlie Simpson, Larry Bell, Manton Scott, Jim Maltman. Second row, left to right: Chris Pollak, George Horton, Sandy Vietor, Joe Duplin (coach), Doug Blanding.
  - Men's sailing, spring, 1970; UA046.003.037.00054 (Box 37)
    - Tufts Sailing team, fall, 1970; UA046.003.037.00054.00001; Unknown (Box 37)
      Front row, from left to right: Dave Johnson, Bill Garfield (co-captain), Chris Andon (co-captain), Don Cundy. Back row, from left to right: Rich Reines, Andy Edelstein, Doug Blanding, Chris Pollak, Sandy Vietor, Joe Duplin (sailing master).
  - Men's sailing, fall, 1970; UA046.003.037.00055 (Box 37)
  - Men's sailing, 1971 -- 1972; UA046.003.037.00056 (Box 37)
  - Men's sailing, 1971; UA046.003.037.00057 (Box 37)
    - Tufts sailing team, fall, 1971; UA046.003.037.00057.00001 (Box 37)
      Front row, from left to right: Mac Cunningham, Manton Scott, Jim Maltman, Ken Hurd, Roger Newberry, Mark Sussman, Glenn Bell. Second row, from left to right: Larry Bell, Don Cundy, Joel Higginson, Sandy Vietor (captain), Lou Libby, Ken Tye, George Class. Third row, from left to right: Chris Pollack, Geoff Clayton, George Norton, Andy Fortunka, Rich Marchand, Charlie Simpson, Joe Duplin (coach). Fall 1971 Tufts University sailing team was rated number 1 in the United States by "Soundings" magazine.
  - Men's sailing, spring, 1971; UA046.003.037.00058 (Box 37)
  - Men's sailing, 1972; UA046.003.037.00059 (Box 37)
    - Varsity sailing team, 1972; UA046.003.037.00059.00001; Unknown (Box 37)
      Group photograph of the Tufts University varsity sailing team, fall 1972.
      Front row (L-R): Manton Scott, George Horton (captain), Jim Maltman, Roger Newberry, Dave Archibald, Joe Duplin (coach) Back row (L-R): Peter Wells, George Glass, Andy Shepard, Dave barrett, Alan Howell
  - Men's sailing, spring, 1972; UA046.003.037.00060 (Box 37)
    - Freshman sailing team, 1972; UA046.003.037.00060.00001; Unknown (Box 37)
      Group picture of the Tufts freshman sailing team, spring 1972 First row (L-R): Dave Winkler, Alan Howell (captain), Andy Hawks, Dave Archibald Second row: Joe Duplin (coach), Peter Wells, Dave barrett, Andy Shepard, Bill Garfield (assistant coach)
      Student activities; Athletics; Sailing; Sailing (CoEd); photographic print; Dept. of Athletics
  - Men's and women's sailing, 1973 -- 1974; UA046.003.037.00061 (Box 37)
    - Tufts sailing team, 1973 -- 1974; UA046.003.037.00061.00001; Unknown (Box 37)
      Group picture of the Tufts sailing team from 1973-1974.
  - Men's and women's sailing, 1974 -- 1975; UA046.003.037.00062 (Box 37)
    - Roger 'Sam' Altreuter and Dave Kellogg, co-captains of the sailing team, 1975; UA046.003.037.00062.00001; Lapides, Susan (Box 37)
      Roger 'Sam' Altreuter (L.) and Dave Kellogg (R.), co-captains of the sailing team, 1974-1975.
      Student activities; Athletics; Sailing; photographic print; Altreuter, Roger 'Sam'; Kellogg, Dave; Dept. of Athletics
    - Cynthia Palladino and Neal Fowler, 1975; UA046.003.037.00062.00002; Lapides, Susan (Box 37)
      Cynthia Palladino (L.) and Neal Fowler (R.) in fall 1975.
      Student activities; Athletics; Sailing; photographic print; Palladino, Cynthia; Fowler, Neal; Dept. of Athletics
  - Men's and women's sailing, 1970 -- 1976; UA046.003.037.00063 (Box 37)
    - Sailing coach Joe Duplin, 1970; UA046.003.037.00063.00001; Bogis, John (Box 37)
      People; Athletics; Sailing; Coaches (Athletics); photographic print; Duplin, Joe; Tufts University; Dept. of Athletics
    - Tufts sailing team members with Jumbo banner, 1976; UA046.003.037.00063.00002; Lapides, Susan (Box 37)
      Unidentified group holding banner.
      People; Athletics; Sailing (CoEd); photographic print; Tufts University; Dept. of Athletics
    - Unidentified pair on boat, 1976; UA046.003.037.00063.00003; Lapides, Susan (Box 37)
      Unidentified pair on boat.
    - Tufts sailing team, 1976; UA046.003.037.00063.00004; Lapides, Susan (Box 37)
      Unidentified group with coach, Joe Duplin.
      People; Athletics; Sailing (CoEd); photographic print; Duplin, Joe; Tufts University; Dept. of Athletics
  - Women's sailing, 1975 -- 1976; UA046.003.037.00064 (Box 37)
  - Men's sailing, 1976; UA046.003.037.00065 (Box 37)
    - Sailboats, 1976; UA046.003.037.00065.00001; Lapides, Susan (Box 37)
      Athletics; Sailboats; Sailing; photographic print; Tufts University; Dept. of Athletics
    - Roger Altreuter, Houston Award winner, 1976; UA046.003.037.00065.00002; Medeiras, Fred (Box 37)
      Roger "Sam" Altreuter, 1976 Houston Award winner.
      People; Athletics; Sailing; photographic print; Altreuter, Roger 'Sam'; Tufts University
  - Men's and women's sailing, 1976 -- 1977; UA046.003.037.00066 (Box 37)
    - Unidentified pair on dock, 1976; UA046.003.037.00066.00001; Lapides, Susan (Box 37)
      Unidentified pair.
  - Women's sailing, 1976 -- 1977; UA046.003.037.00067 (Box 37)
    - Women's sailing team, 1976 -- 1977; UA046.003.037.00067.00001; Unknown (Box 37)
      Group portrait of the 1976-1977 women's sailing team.
      Student activities; Athletics; Sailing; Sailing (Women's); photographic print; Eagan, Patty; Baxter, Diana; Kenerson, Marie; Dierdorff, Susan; Mitchell, Anne; Dept. of Athletics
  - Women's sailing, 1977; UA046.003.037.00068 (Box 37)
  - Men's and women's sailing, 1977 -- 1978; UA046.003.037.00069 (Box 37)
    - Tufts sailing team, 1977 -- 1978; UA046.003.037.00069.00001; Unknown (Box 37)
      Front row, from left to right: Paul Duane, Dave Peck, Jeff Schwarz (captain), Jamie McCreary, Ted Scott. Second row, left to right: Stewart Neff, Sam Philbrick, Maurice Kurg, Andrew Menkart, Doug McKeige, Anne Mitchell. Third row, left to right: Chris Fowler, Mike Zavell, Stu Johnstone, Liz Ferenbach, Cathy Hausman, Connie Hufferd, Jim Miller. Fourth row, left to right: Betsy Gelenitis, Paula Spizziri, Geoffrey Wheeler, Beverly Brine, Joe Petrucci, Rowena Nelson, Dave Nickerson, Pam Slater, Susy Dierdorff, Joe Duplin (coach), Trina Nueman, Tina McVeigh, Fran Charles, Sue Cripe.
  - Women's sailing, 1977 -- 1978; UA046.003.037.00070 (Box 37)
    - Tufts women's sailing team, 1977 -- 1978; UA046.003.037.00070.00001; Unknown (Box 37)
      From left to right: Rosemary Macero, Rowena Nelson, Paula Spizziri, Marie-Laure Fourlinnie, Mark Mueller (coach), Betsy Gelenitis, Susan Dierdorff (captain), Anne Mitchell.
      People; Athletics; Sailing (Women's); photographic print; Tufts University; Dept. of Athletics
  - Men's sailing, 1979; UA046.003.037.00071 (Box 37)
  - Men's and women's sailing, 1975 -- 1979; UA046.003.037.00072 (Box 37)
    - Peter Commette, 1979; UA046.003.037.00072.00001; Unknown (Box 37)
      People; Students; photographic print; Tufts University
    - Two sailing team members, 1976; UA046.003.037.00072.00002; Lapides, Susan (Box 37)
      Unidentified pair on dock.
    - Unknown pair and sailboat, 1979; UA046.003.037.00072.00003; Lapides, Susan (Box 37)
      From left to right: unidentified person, Fran Charles.
    - Martha Winsche and Jamie McCreary, 1975; UA046.003.037.00072.00004; Lapides, Susan (Box 37)
    - Unidentified group, 1979; UA046.003.037.00072.00005; Unknown (Box 37)
  - Men's and women's sailing, 1979 -- 1981; UA046.003.037.00073 (Box 37)
    - Unidentified pair sailing, 1980; UA046.003.037.00073.00001; Costerus, Alec (Box 37)
      People; Athletics; Sailing (Women's); photographic print; Tufts University
    - Unidentified woman sailing, 1980; UA046.003.037.00073.00002; Landau, Steven (Box 37)
    - Betsy Gelenitis, 1979; UA046.003.037.00073.00003; Lapides, Susan (Box 37)
    - Men sailing, 1980; UA046.003.037.00073.00004; Unknown (Box 37)
      From left to right: Marshall Duane and Mike Loeb in Dutchman.
      People; Athletics; Sailing (Men's); photographic print; Tufts University; Dept. of Athletics
  - Indoor track, UA046.003.037.00074 (Box 37)
  - Outdoor track, UA046.003.037.00075 (Box 37)
  - Roy Philips Memorial Trophy, UA046.003.037.00076 (Box 37)
  - Track, UA046.003.037.00077 (Box 37)
  - Track, 1906; UA046.003.037.00078 (Box 37)
  - Track, 1908 -- 1909; UA046.003.037.00079 (Box 37)
  - Track, 1910 -- 1911; UA046.003.037.00080 (Box 37)
  - Track, 1913 -- 1914; UA046.003.037.00081 (Box 37)
  - Track, 1919; UA046.003.037.00082 (Box 37)
  - Track, 1921; UA046.003.037.00083 (Box 37)
  - Track, 1928; UA046.003.037.00084 (Box 37)
  - Indoor track, 1934 -- 1935; UA046.003.037.00085 (Box 37)
  - Track, 1935 -- 1936; UA046.003.037.00086 (Box 37)
  - Track, 1939; UA046.003.037.00087 (Box 37)
  - Indoor Track, 1939 -- 1940; UA046.003.037.00088 (Box 37)
  - Track, 1940 -- 1959; UA046.003.037.00089 (Box 37)
  - Outdoor track, 1940; UA046.003.037.00090 (Box 37)
  - Track, 1940; UA046.003.037.00091 (Box 37)
  - Indoor track, 1940 -- 1941; UA046.003.037.00092 (Box 37)
  - Track, 1941; UA046.003.037.00093 (Box 37)
  - Indoor Track MVP Award, 1942 -- 1943; UA046.003.037.00094 (Box 37)
  - Outdoor track, 1943; UA046.003.037.00095 (Box 37)
  - Outdoor track, 1945; UA046.003.037.00096 (Box 37)
    - Ed Palmeri, 1945; UA046.003.037.00096.00001; Dwight Davis Photo (Box 37)
      Member of IC4A relay champ, 1945; intercollegiate outdoor 440 yard champ, 1945.
      People; Athletics; Outdoor Track (Men's); photographic print
  - Track, 1945 -- 1946; UA046.003.037.00097 (Box 37)
  - Outdoor track, 1946; UA046.003.037.00098 (Box 37)
  - Track, 1946; UA046.003.037.00099 (Box 37)
  - Indoor track, 1946 -- 1947; UA046.003.037.00100 (Box 37)
  - Track, 1946 -- 1947; UA046.003.037.00101 (Box 37)
  - Outdoor track, 1947; UA046.003.037.00102 (Box 37)